<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STH</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">DrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Hello</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    //-----Array of "Law for Woman" -----
    <string-array name="lawListGroup">
        <item>Acid Attack (Section 326A and 326B)</item>
        <item>Rape (Section 375,376,376A,376B,376C,376D and 376E)</item>
        <item>Kidnapping and Abduction for different purposes (Sections 363–373)</item>
        <item>Murder, Dowry Death, Abutment of Suicide (Section 302, 304B and 306)</item>
        <item>Dowry Prohibition Act (Section 498A)</item>
        <item>Cruelty by husband or his relatives (Section 498A)</item>
        <item>Outraging the modesty of Women (Section 354)</item>
        <item>Sexual Harassment (Section 354A)</item>
        <item>Assault on women with intent to disrobe a woman (Section 354B)</item>
        <item>Voyeurism (Section 354C)</item>
        <item>Stalking (Section 354D)</item>
        <item>Word, Gesture or act intended to insult the modesty of a woman (Section 509)</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lawListChild">
        <item>
            The Criminal Law (Amendment) Act, 2013 incorporated Section 326A and 326B with an intend to make specific provision for
            punishment in the case of Acid Attack. \n\n
            Section 326A focuses on voluntarily causing grievous hurt by using acid. In the view of this section, whosoever causes
            permanent or partial damage or burns, disfigures or disables any part of the body of a person or causes grievous hurt by
            throwing or administering acid with an intention to cause such injury or hurt will be punished with imprisonment of at
            least ten years which may extended to life imprisonment with fine. \n\n
            Section 326B has more legislative focus on the act of throwing or attempting to throw acid with the intention of causing
            grievous hurt. The punishment under this section is imprisonment of not less than five years with fine which may extend
            up to seven years.
        </item>
        <item>
            Section 375, IPC defines rape. In simple terms, the offence of rape is the ravishment of a woman, without her consent, by
            force, fraud or fear.It is an obnoxious act of highest degree which violates the right to privacy and sanctity of a female.
            Apart from being a dehumanising and perverted act, it is also an unlawful interface in the personal life of a woman which
            is an intense blow on the honour, dignity, reputation and self-esteem of a woman. \n\n
            Section 375 includes:\n
            1.Actus Reus: There must be sexual intercourse, as understood in terms of the provisions of Section 375 (a) to (d), with
            a woman by a man. \n\n
            2.Mens Rea: The sexual intercourse must be under any of the seven circumstances as given under Section 375.\n\n
            Section 376 provides for committing the heinous crime of rape. This section is divided into two sub-sections.\n\n
            Section 376(1) provides a minimum sentence of seven years of imprisonment that may extend to life imprisonment
            and fine.\n\n
            Section 376(2) provides punishment not less than ten years of imprisonment but may extend to imprisonment for life or death
            or fine.\n\n
            Section 376D lays down the punishment for gang rape. Where a woman is raped by more than one person acting in furtherance
            of a common intention, each of them shall be liable for the offence of rape and shall be punished with rigours imprisonment
            for not less than twenty years which may extend to lifetime imprisonment and fine.
        </item>
        <item>
            Section 363 in IPC defines Punishment for Kidnapping. Whoever kidnaps any person or from lawful guardianship, shall be
            punished with imprisonment of either description for a term which may extend to seven years, and shall also be liable
            to fine.\n\n
            Section 373 in IPC defines buying minor for purposes of prostitution, etc. Whoever buys, hires or otherwise obtains
            possession of any person under the age of 18 years with intent that such person shall at any age be employed or used for
            the purpose of prostitution or illicit intercourse with any person shall be punished with imprisonment of either
            description for a term which may extend to ten years, and shall also be liable to fine.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dowry deaths and bride burning are sinful act which are still prevailing in the Indian society. It is a symptom of a
            special social illness and are unfortunate development of our society. For this serious matter, the special provision
            was inserted under IPC through Section 304B which deals with dowry deaths.\n\n
            Section 304B defines dowry death. It lays down its punishment which is not less than seven years and may extend to
            life imprisonment.
        </item>
        <item>
            A separate chapter of IPC deals with the issues of cruelty by a husband or his relatives under Section 498A. The objective
            behind the introduction of this provision was to punish the husband and his relatives who torture, ill-treat and harass
            a woman with a view to force her or any other person to her to meet any unlawful demands.\n\n
            This section has given a new dimension to the concept of cruelty which is the essence of this section, for the purpose
            of matrimonial relief. Not every type of cruelty will attract Section 498A. It has been mentioned under the section that
            what kind of cruelty is included hereby.\n\n
            The punishment for this offence is imprisonment for a term which may extend to three years with fine.
        </item>
        <item>
            Section 498A is intended to prevent the giving or receiving of a dowry. Under the Dowry Prohibition Act, dowry includes
            property, goods, or money given by either party to the marriage, by the parents of either party, or by anyone else in connection
            with the marriage.\n\n
            The punishment could be imprisonment for minimum 5 years and a fine more than ₹15,000 or the value of the dowry received,
            whichever is higher.The Act provides the penalty for directly or indirectly demanding dowry and provides for a penalty involving
            a prison term of not less than 6 months and extendable up to two years along with a fine of ₹10,000.
        </item>

        <item>
            Section 354, IPC deals with the offence of molestation i.e. assault to woman with intent to outrage her modesty.
            This section aims to protect women against any sort of indecent or fifthly behaviour by others which is derogatory to her
            modesty. This offence is not just against the individual but also against the society and public morality. Therefore, if
            any person uses criminal force upon a woman an intention to outrage the modesty of a woman, he is deemed to be punished
            with an imprisonment of not less than one year which may extended up to five years with fine.\n\n
            It is not specifically defined under IPC that what constitutes an outrage to modesty of women. Modesty is said to
            be outraged by such an act of offender which shocks and recognizes as an insult to female decency and dignity.
        </item>
        <item>
            According to Section 354A IPC, Sexual Harassment is the: \n
            1.Unwelcome touching or other physical contact.\n
            2.Asking or demanding sex or any other sexual activity.\n
            3.Making remarks which are of a sexual nature.\n
            4.Showing pornographic material which may include videos, magazines, books, etc.\n\n
            The punishment for the first three kinds of sexual harassment is three years and for the forth type which is one year.
        </item>
        <item>
            Section 354B penalises the offence of assaulting or using criminal force to a woman or abetting any such act with an
            intention to disrobe or compel her to be naked, with a punishment not less than three years which may extend to seven
            years with a fine. This is gender specific offence i.e. only man can be punished under this section.
        </item>
        <item>
            This offence came into existence after Nirbhaya Rape Cape, 2012. It is mentioned under Section 354C IPC.
            The word "Voyeurism" means appeasement derived from observing the genital or sexual acts of others usually secretly.
            This provision is divided in two different parts. Firstly, when a person watches or captures image of a woman engaging
            in some private act and Secondly, when the person disseminate or spread such images. \n\n
            The first offence is punishable with imprisonment of not less than one year which may extend up to three years with fine.
            The second offence is punishable with imprisonment of not less than three years which may extend up to seven years with fine.
        </item>
        <item>
            Section 354D IPC talks about the term "Stalking" which generally means tha act of following or trying to contact
            despite disinterest of woman. This section contains two offence:\n
            1. Where a man follows or contact or attempts to contact a woman repeatedly despite her clear indication of disinterest.\n
            2. Where a man monitors the use by a woman of the internet, email, or any other form of electronic communication.\n\n
            For the first offence the punishment is imprisonment foe a term which may extend to three years with fine.
            The punishment for second conviction may extend up to five years of imprisonment with fine.
        </item>
        <item>
            An act which is done intending to insult the modesty of woman which may not necessarily involve any physical force is
            brought under the shade of this provision through Section 509. This section intends to deter any kind of aggregation into
            a modesty of women whether by any word, gesture or act or by intruding upon the privacy of such woman. This section is also
            referred as the "Eve Teasing Section".\n\n
            Any person who commits an offence under Section 509 shall be punished with simple imprisonment for a term which may
            extend to three years with fine.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //-----Array of "Tips from Escape"-----
    <string-array name="threatQueStr">
        <item>
            1. What should a woman do if she finds herself alone in the company of a strange male as she prepares to enter a list in a High Rise apartment late at night?
        </item>
        <item>
            2. What to do if a stranger tries to attack you when you are alone at your house?
        </item>
        <item>
            3. What should do while taking Auto or Taxi at Night?
        </item>
        <item>
            4. What if the driver turns into a street he is not supposed too and you feel you are entering a danger zone?
        </item>
        <item>
            5. What to do if you are stalked at night?
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="threatAnsStr">
        <item>
            Enter the lift. If you need to need to reach the 12th floor, press all the buttons up to your destination.
            No one will dare attack you in a lift that stops on every floor.
        </item>
        <item>
            Run into the Kitchen. Use Chilli Powder, Turmeric Powder and Knife for self defence. If you are not able to
            find anything, then you can protect yourself by throwing Plates, Dishes and other Utensils.
        </item>
        <item>
            Before getting into an auto at night, note the registration and number and send it to the person to whom you believe i.e.
            family, close friend,etc. You also have to tell the registration number over the phone in that language so the driver will also understand.\n\n
            If no one is answering your call then put your phone on vibrate and pretend that you are talking to them. You can also talk over the phone
            when you are in the taxi or auto.So the driver knows that someone has his details and he will be in serious trouble if anything goes wrong.
        </item>
        <item>
            Use you purse to attack or use your dupatta to wrap around his neck and pull him back. Within seconds, he will feel chocked and helpless.
            In case you do not have your dupatta then pull back his T-shirt or shirt to choke him.
        </item>
        <item>
            Enter into any shop and explain your situation and ask for help or else take help from any house. If it is late night and shops are closed
            then enter into the ATM . ATM centers always have close circuit television.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //-----Array of "Tips of Safety"-----
    <string name="safetyStr">
        <item>
            1. Avoid more usage of phones, this makes you more alert.\n\n
            2. While travelling through auto, make sure to share auto number with someone.\n\n
            3. If you booked a cab, always share your coordinates with someone.\n\n
            4. Avoid going to isolated areas with no CCTV camera.\n\n
            5. Learn some Self Defence Techniques to protect yourself.\n\n
            6. For safety, make sure to carry small knife or Pepper Spray.
        </item>
    </string>

    <string name="socialStr">
        <item>
            1. Do not updates you personal data and locations on social media.\n\n
            2. Do not share post which contains your email address, home address or mobile numbers.\n\n
            3. Avoid posting your photos which can be use for editing.\n\n
            4. Avoid posting day to day life style or life schedule on social media.\n\n
            5. Avoid accepting requests from unknown person.
        </item>
    </string>

    //-----About App-----
    <string name="aboutApp">
        <item>
            Our application is for girls and women who are living or travelling alone or who are facing some problems and does not
            have any idea about what to do to handle this situation.\n\n
            In our application we have provided many Laws for women with details. So women will be aware about laws and if required
            they can also handle their situation.\n\n
            We have also provided tips for safety and tips to escape from threats. Also there are listed NGOs for women welfare
            and development.\n\n
            There are video for self defence technique so any women will be able to protect themselves if she is living alone or
            travelling alone.\n\n
            This app also has SOS so any the listed people know about your location and easy reach you if you are in danger.\n\n
            For feedback and query send mail on:\n\n"shethehumanapplication@gmail.com"
        </item>
    </string>

</resources>